{ "questions": 
  [
    {
      "question" : "What's the name of our CEO?",
      "answer" : "Melissa",
      "wrongAnswers" : ["Lisa","Thomas","Laura"]
    },
    {
      "question" : "What's our favourite color?",
      "answer" : "Green",
      "wrongAnswers" : ["Red","Black","Pink"]
    },
    {
      "question" : "Where are our headquarters?",
      "answer" : "Nuremberg",
      "wrongAnswers" : ["Prague","London","Paris"]
    },
    {
      "question" : "What's our official chatting tool?",
      "answer" : "Rocket Chat",
      "wrongAnswers" : ["IRC","Messenger","Slack"]
    },
    {
      "question" : "What's our favourite pet?",
      "answer" : "Chameleon",
      "wrongAnswers" : ["Cat","Dog","Lizard"]
    },
    {
      "question" : "Do we allow remote working?",
      "answer" : "Yes",
      "wrongAnswers" : ["No","Only on Fridays","Only in Germany"]
    },
    {
      "question" : "What's the last released version of the SUSE Linux Enterprise Server?",
      "answer" : "15 SP1",
      "wrongAnswers" : ["15 SP2","12 SP4","11 SP4"]
    },
    {
      "question" : "What's the name of openSUSE rolling release?",
      "answer" : "Tumbleweed",
      "wrongAnswers" : ["Tumblewide","Leap","SLES"]
    },
    {
      "question" : "When was released the first version of SUSE (S.u.S.E. Linux 4.2)?",
      "answer" : "1996",
      "wrongAnswers" : ["1988","1992","2005"]
    },
    {
      "question" : "How we call our pet?",
      "answer" : "Geeko",
      "wrongAnswers" : ["Greeny","Susy","Leap"]
    },
    {
      "question" : "What is bug bsc#547233 about?",
      "answer" : "Cold fusion",
      "wrongAnswers" : ["Time travel","SUSE Manager","SLE"]
    },
    {
      "question" : "What's short name of the annual SUSE Conference?",
      "answer" : "SUSECon",
      "wrongAnswers" : ["GreenCon","SUSEConf","Geekcon"]
    },
    {
      "question" : "For what is the slogan 'Smarter innovation that puts you back in control'?",
      "answer" : "SUSE",
      "wrongAnswers" : ["Brexit","Tante Suzie","Sushi"]
    },
    {
      "question" : "What manages your network interfaces on SLES?",
      "answer" : "Wicked",
      "wrongAnswers" : ["Vicious","Crooked","Network Ballader"]
    }
  ]
}